Testing the .asss files inside the video tag
Subs adapted from Dattebayo.
For more episodes -> http://innerbleach.com
Karaoke FX (Script) -> Ombre Noire (Fx)
Timed by superjose
Well people. Welcome to the V2 releases!!! hope you enjoy them!
Kasumi-Ooji, a high-ranking noble family in Soul Society, is feuding over who will be the next clan leader.
Lurichiyo, princess of the Kasumi-Ooji family, has come to the real world.
Ichigo was roped into becoming her bodyguard and de facto playmate, while Lurichiyo herself has no idea that her life is in danger.
At the same time, in Soul Society, the 3rd Squad welcomed Amagai Shuusuke as their new captain, and is in the midst of a new mission.
It went that way.
Corner it!
We lost sight of it!
See anything?
This way!
Hurry! Don't lose sight of it!
Good boy...
Got it.
3rd Seat Kifune, well done!
Vice-Captain Kira, you were trying too hard.
Vice-Captain, confirmation please.
Oh, yes... Right!
3 yo
Missing Male Cat
No doubt about it. This is the cat.
Then we've finished the mission.
But, why the heck did we have to search for some noble's lost cat?
Yesterday we had to guard the kimono material shop.
All of our missions have been like this lately.
I'm sure the Captain has his reasons for this.
What do you think, Vice-Captain Kira?
Uhm... Well... I don't really know.
I'd rather do missions that are actually worth our time!
I know, I know. Anyways, how about we all go grab a drink?
Sounds good!
Let's go!
Are you coming, Vice-Captain Kira?
I... have to gather up the reports.
Excuse me!
All done, Izuru?
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing...
It's just... that I wasn't expecting you to call me by my first name.
I thought it'd be a good idea to call everyone by their first names to relax the tension between us, but..
Bad idea?
Well, I'm not really used to it, so...
I see. I thought was on to something, too...
I guess I'll think something else up.
Here are today's reports.
Oh, also...
About tomorrow...
What does "repairing the 12th Squad's pavilion walls" mean?
Repairing walls means repairing walls.
That's not what I meant!
Why are we doing menial things like that?!
Everyone in the squad-
Kira, it may hurt to hear this, but the 3rd Squad was betrayed by its former captain, Ichimaru Gin.
You get what I mean?
It's hard to regain trust once you've lost it.
Now, I don't think doing things like this will smooth things over quickly, but it's better than nothing.
Relax, Kira.
I get the feeling that Ichimaru Gin had too much influence over this squad when I look at you.
You aren't Ichimaru.
No one's going to ask the same things of you that they did of him.
Rallying around a charismatic captain is one way of doing things,
but only having one pillar for support makes us weak when it crumbles.
That's why I'd like to build a new squad, where you, myself and Kifune form three supporting pillars.
So, what's 3rd Seat Kifune up to?
He's out drinking with the guys.
It looks like Inose and everyone finally accepted 3rd Seat Kifune after that last battle.
I see.
On that note, I think I'll call it quits for the day.
If you're still feeling a bit out of it, you should go have some fun, too.
Huh? No.
See you later then!
Thanks for all your hard work.
Today we're going to try a different type of training.
Lately, there's been an increase in powerful foes, including Menos.
(Dangai: Severing World / Precipice World)
Such as our battle in the Dangai.
If you don't work together as a team from here on,
you'll die.
But, we're training so that doesn't happen.
Kifune.
Yes, sir.
Take whatever color headband you like.
Anyone wearing the color I call out will become the enemy.
Everyone else must form groups of three and surround the enemy!
However, I will change the color for who the enemy is.
The moment I call out a different color, the position for enemy and comrade is going to change.
This is a special training that will strengthen your ability to make decisions quickly.
Kifune, I want you to join in and act as leader for everyone.
Yes, sir!
I'll participate, too.
Kira. That's okay.
Eh?
I used this training exercise back with my patrol unit.
I'd prefer to have Kifune lead since he's already used to this exercise.
Yes, sir.
Sorry.
Let's go!
Yes, sir!
Purple for starters!
Uh...
Aida, come with me!
Yes!
Inose, come in from the rear!
Next is yellow!
Next is red!
Good! You've got it!
Amazing!
When did everyone learn to move together as a team?
Man, Captain Amagai's drills are unlike anything we've ever done before!
Captain Ichimaru never did group training like this!
It really feels like we can fight effectively when we work together!
Yeah! I see captain Amagai in a whole new light now!
Same for 3rd Seat Kifune!
He's way more reliable than Vice-Captain Kira!
You think he'll become our vice-captain at some point?
Idiot! That's going too far!
Vice-Captain Kira...
Yes... 3rd Seat Kifune.
Aren't you going to say anything?
Uh... Nah..
I see.
I mean, you're pretty amazing, 3rd Seat Kifune!
Not at all. It's nothing compared to you and how you kept the 3rd Squad together up until now.
That's not true.
Everyone's already accepted you, more than they do me.
But-
Whatever! Just let it go!
I'm sorry. I guess I'm a bit tired.
Excuse me.
More!
That's the way to chug it down, Kira!
There! Have some more sake!
Man, you're really inhaling it!
Something happen?
It's fine.
The 3rd Squad is going to change!
It'll totally be different than it used to!
Ok! get it!
The atmosphere around the squad changes when you get a different captain.
Trust me, I know what you're going through.
Thanks to Captain Amagai, the 3rd Squad's ranks have been improving.
I'd say he's done a pretty good job for such a short amount of time.
I...
...think so, too.
That's no good!
With an attitude like that, the new 3rd Seat that just came in... what's-his-face, uh-
3rd. Seat Kifune
That's right! He's going to take your spot as vice-captain!
Well, no one believes in me...
Iba-san!
Shit, he stepped on a mine right there!
Welcome! We've got two customers!
-Welcome! -Welcome!
Can we have a private room?
Yes! Absolutely!
Speaking of the devil...
Why is he with Captain Kyouraku?
Bottom up!
I must say, I'm happy the famous new captain invited me out for a little drinking!
I'm still inexperienced at this.
Talking with my senpai is also part of my job.
So, what do you need from me?
I won't beat around the bush.
Good! I hate it when people talk without saying anything.
It has to do with the 13 Protection Squads.
Would it be possible for us to improve coordination between the different squads?
That'd be pretty tough.
I'm sure that it would be difficult to staff right now, but at this rate-
Don't get so worked up.
Ah... I'm sorry.
But I don't think it's a bad idea.
You see my point?
Amagai-kun, for a kid of your age, you're really using your head.
Oh, it's nothing!
You know, you should tell Ukitake about this idea of yours, not just me.
The 13th Squad's Captain?
Yeah. It's not like I won't help too, but I'm kinda bad at taking the initiative on things.
Why don't you invite Ukitake next time too, and we can all discuss it together?
Yes! It would be my pleasure!
Okay! Then let's toast to it and get going!
Huh? You haven't drunk anything?
Well, um..
Here!
Here it goes!
Oi, oi, oi! Don't tell me... You can't drink?! For real?!
Vice-Captain Kira, there were no abnormalities in East District 7.
Good work, 3rd Seat Kifune.
The Court of Pure Souls is completely secure.
Is it?
Glad to hear it.
Is something wrong?
Oh, no, nothing at all.
Oh, yeah! I should make us some tea!
Vice-Captain Kira.
What is it?
I know this is going to come across as rude,
but why do you always seem like you don't have confidence in yourself?
Well I...
Um...
It's an emergency message!
A suspicious shadow in the execution ground ruins...
Vice-Captain!
Vice-Captain! 3rd Seat!
Um, you are?
I'm Seko Shinta.
I'm sorry. I didn't remember your name.
It's okay. I'm a new recruit and I'm not even a seated officer.
Where did it...?
Right near that hole.
I saw a suspicious shadow earlier and tried to chase after it, but...
What's wrong?
Well, it looked like it disappeared into that hole.
Is this the old execution ground ruins?
You're done for if you fall in, right?
At this rate, he'll-!
Vice-Captain!
3rd Seat Kifune...
Are you all right?
More or less.
Good. Now, why did the ground suddenly collapsed?
There's no way we can climb out.
There should be an exit somewhere around here where they would bring in and take out prisoners.
Let's look around for it.
Right!
This reiatsu-!
These are-!
What are they doing here?!
There are a lot of them.
But, if they are all as weak as this...
Stop!
Rage, Reppuu!
(Reppuu: Violent Wind)
3rd Seat Kifune...
Not good! If these Hollow get outside-!
What are you?
Raise your head, Wabisuke!
(Wabisuke: The penitent one)
What are you doing, 3rd Seat Kifune?
I'm just finishing the Hollow.
But Seko is-!
That fool was unable to fulfill his job as a Shinigami.
He was captured by the enemy.
He has done a wonderful job of dishonoring himself.
When taking up the mantle of a Shinigami, you must have the resolve to die.
Trash that only gets in our way and endangers others, has no right to live.
What are you saying?!
Why are you trying to save that trash?
You're too soft!
What?!
That's why you were unable to prevent the previous captain's rebellion.
Isn't that right?!
That's...
I...
I see you lack resolve as well.
Hey!
You guys okay?
Captain Amagai!
Captain!
We've got an injured Shinigami who was nearly absorbed by a Hollow.
Hang on! We're sending down help!
Thank you!
Captain, what happened to the Hollow that escaped to the surface?
Yeah. Some soldiers nearby noticed them and informed me.
We took care of all of them.
I see. My apologies
We've taken Seko to the 4th Squad's facility,
but he was hurt badly, and they aren't sure if they'll be able to save him...
I see.
And about the ground that caved in...
It looks like someone rigged it beforehand so it could crumble easily.
Did either of you see anything?
Is something wrong, guys?
Oh, um...
No, it's nothing...
Are you sure? You're both acting strange...
You two! What have you done to the Hollows I was experimenting on?
Those Hollow belonged to the 12th Squad?
Yes. Someone appears to have unlocked the doors and released them.
Who would do that?
How do you expect me to know?!
Nemu, this is your fault for not properly securing the area, you bumbling dunce!
I'm terribly sorry, Mayuri-sama.
Blast, I'm so mad!
And you, 3rd Squad Captain! Why didn't you capture them alive?!
Now I can't conduct my experiments!
Easy, easy! Don't get angry!
What?
No one's there...
The door must be getting old...
Abarai-kun, why were you together with Iba-san today?
He dragged me along so we could talk about the hardships the Shinigami Men's Association's going through.
Yeah, the Men's Association doesn't stand a chance against the Women's.
You said it.
They keep messing with us because of attitudes like that!
Shinigami Illustrated Picture Book.
What's up, Byakuya?
What did you wanna talk about?
Kurosaki Ichigo...
I found Icchi!
Yachiru, what're you doing here?!
I messed around with Byak-kun's house and made secret tunnels!
I'll show them to you, Icchi!
I get it, I get it...
Hurry! Hurry!
Sorry, Byakuya.
This way, this way!
How long do you plan on saying my name without adding the proper suffix-